4umf.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - 4UMF : 4UMF

**Privacy Policy**

**Last updated: February 10, 2013.**

4UMF.com (also referred to herein as “4 Ur Media Fix,” the “Site”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it at all times. This Internet Privacy Notice (the “Privacy Notice”) explains how we collect, use, and safeguard information on this Site. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. 

**By visiting 4UMF.com, you acknowledge and accept the practices, terms, and conditions described in this Privacy Notice and the 4UMF Conditions of Use (the “Legal Team”), which is located at the**[ **URLhttp://4umf.com/legal-team/**](http://4umf.com/legal-team/) **and agree that any and all disputes, including, without limitation, those disputes arising over privacy, between you and 4UMF.com, its parent company(ies), subsidiary(ies), affiliated companies, principals, owners, board members, employees, contributors, advertisers, sponsors, affiliates, partners, and any of their licensees, successors, and assignees, will be subject to terms and conditions of this Privacy Notice and/or the Conditions of Use, as applicable**.

By visiting 4UMF.com after we post any changes to this Privacy Notice and/or the Conditions of Use, you accept the Privacy Notice and/or the Conditions of Use, as applicable, as modified.

**Your Georgia Privacy Rights**

Georgia Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “[Shine The Light](http://www.atlantafixture.com/StaticContent.aspx?StaticContentKeyword=privacy-statement)” law,  permits our customers who are Georgia residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.  If you are a Georgia resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request by electronic mail to:

[[manager@4umf.com](mailto:manager@4umf.com)]

**What Personal Information About Customers Does 4UMF.com Collect?**

The information we learn about our customers helps us personalize and continually improve at the service and features of 4UMF.com. Here are the types of information we collect:

  * **Information You Give Us:**  We receive and may store any personal and financial information you enter on the Site or may give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our services and features. We may use the information that you provide for a variety of purposes, including to respond to your requests, to customize future options for you, to improve the overall quality of the Site, and to communicate with you, among other things.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
